Can you turn it on? Fine.
你会开机吗? 没事.
First you turn the computer on. Like this.
首先你要打开电脑. 像这样.
Then you turn on the monitor.
然后你打开显示器.
Then you turn on the printer.
再然后你打开打印机.
So far, so good. Now, what?
到目前为止, 一切顺利. 现在,干什么?
You open the program.
你打开程序.
Either click on the icon,
可以用鼠标点击图标,
or type the command on the keyboard.
或者敲入命令 用键盘.
OK. So I hit here to...
OK. 所以我点这儿来...
What happened? I lost it. It's gone.
发生了什么? 我把它弄丢了. 不见了.
Relax. When that happens.
放松. 这种时候,
just hit these two keys.
只需要敲这两个键.
Why?
Well. It says to the computer,
Well. 这是在告诉计算机,
"Don't do what I just told you to do."
"不要做我刚刚要你做的"
OK.
Go on. Hit those two keys.
继续. 敲这两个键.
OK. I type the correct command, and... hey!
OK. 我敲入正确的指令, 然后...hey!
You're in the program.
你进入程序了.
Great.
太棒了.
That wasn't so hard, was it?
并不太难, 对吗?
Nope. What's next?
Nope. 下一步是什么?
Now just start at the beginning,
现在只要从头开始.
and work your way to the end. Good luck!
学完它. 祝你好运!